RANJITH REDDY ARJULA

SAP ABAP Senior Consultant

Phone: +91 779-960-1166

Email: abap.ranjith@gmail.com

Professional Summary

SAP ABAP Consultant with 10 years of experience in development, conversion, maintenance, and support projects. Proficient in SAP R/3 systems, HANA, and AMSOG. Experienced in managing teams and coordinating with onshore business partners.

Areas of Expertise

- Technical Skills: SAP ABAP, OO ABAP, OData, ABAP on HANA, SAP CAI, SAP BTP RAP

- Functional Areas: SAP MM, SAP PM, SAP FI

Professional Experience

SAP ABAP Consultant

Company: Marathon Petroleum Corporation

Location: Findlay, Ohio

Dates: November 2020 - Present

- Developed several reports related to work order, notification, equipment and functional creation and update process
- Developed report to calculate Annual Estimate report for Measurement Documents
- Enhanced multiple transaction such as IW31, IW21, IW47 etc..
- Implemented enhancements and conversion reports for work orders.
- Implemented proxies for data communication with APM and INTELEX.
- Worked on Winshuttle scripts and created wrapper FMs for the scripts

SAP ABAP Consultant

Company: SAP Labs India

Location: Gurgaon, India

Dates: Multiple Projects (2014 - 2020)

Project: AMSOG (Asset Management Solution for Oil & Gas)

Dates: July 2015 - September 2017, January 2018 - September 2020

- Implemented inspection, subcontracting, assembly, physical inventory processes.
- Developed functionalities for material management, stock reports, and accounting processes.

Project: Product Allocation of Fiori App Management

Client: TERUMO Corporation

Dates: October 2017 - December 2017

• Created OData services and modified UI5 applications for customer data management and mass upload functionality.

Project: PERSON BASED ENTITLEMENT Department of Defense Australia

Dates: November 2014 - July 2015

• Developed OO ABAP classes and enhanced SAP DFPS for personnel entitlement and qualification relationship management.

Education

- Master of Computer Application (MCA)
 Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Hyderabad
- Intermediate in M.P.C
 ABV Jr. College, Jangaon, Warangal
- SSC

Loyola High School, Station Ghanpur, Warangal

Skills

- Technical: SAP ABAP, OO ABAP, OData, ABAP on HANA, SAP CAI, SAP BTP RAP, HANA CDS, C, C++, Core JAVA, JavaScript, Python
- Soft Skills: Ability to work under pressure, multi-tasking, conflict resolution, time management, effective team communication

Achievements

- Received 'SAP Top Partner Award' from SAP Labs.
- Rated 10/10 by customer (Terumo) for application development.

Languages

English, Telugu, Hindi

Personal Information

• Date of Birth: July 09, 1989

• Gender: Male

• Marital Status: Married

• Location: Hyderabad, India